All right. Hello everyone. Uh
this is Pastor Meyers
coming to you live
from
Atlanta.
Yes, it is uh night time. We're actually
heading back to Huntsville
right now and I just wanted to jump I'm
not driving by the way. So, just just in
case anybody asks, the car is not
moving, but I do want to jump on and
just make a couple of quick uh
announcements. This video will only be
up for a little while, then it's going
to come down. Okay. Um, so I got two
announcements I want to I want to share
with you guys. First of all,
announcement number one is my Revelation
in 7 days class. My Revelation in 7 days
class. Um, that class which was supposed
to start today is not starting today
because I am not in Huntsville right
now. So, the class will start tomorrow.
For those of you that signed up for the
for that course, that 7-day course, it
will start tomorrow.
But for those of you that wanted to sign
up for it, there is still time to sign
up for it. And I'm going to put this uh
put the website in the chat for you. Uh
so
it is my photo theology.com
and that's where you can go um to
register for the Revelation in 7 days
course. in that we just finished the
Daniel in seven days course as well as a
photo theology in seven days course. Now
we're doing the revelation course. We're
going to be going through the seven
seals, the seven trumpets, the seven
plagues, and we're not going to be
looking at this from the typical
um uh you know typical perspective.
We'll be looking at this through the
lens of photo theology. So this class is
for those who really want to uh in a
closed environment get deep into the
book of revelation and really understand
the principles, the storyline,
um the patterns,
um the parallels. Uh it's just going to
be a a totally unique study. For those
of you uh that were in my Daniel in 7
days class or my photo theology in 7
days class, you will know that um these
classes were not your typical, you know,
Daniel 2, Daniel 7, Babylon, Meip, Pers,
Greece, Rome wasn't that typical type of
study. Um it was definitely
um uh on a way deeper level. So, I see
you Jay. What's up, Clint? Um, and I
know there are others on here watching.
But anyway, so that's the first
announcement I wanted to make.
And the second announcement that I that
I am preparing to make you guys um
so I have been working on a photo
theology
GPT
and uh I am going to be on in the next
probably as early as next week maybe
even earlier
to do a demonstration of this photo
theology GPT. And I'm super excited
about this GPT because this GPT is based
strictly
on the photo theology principles of
Bible study. And um the other thing
about this GPT is that it is not
designed to study for you. It is
designed to teach you how to study and
think deeper in the scriptures. So I'm
super excited about this. I've kind of
let this out in a small
um you know kind of a little bit by
little bit. I've um given it to to some
of the individuals in either my photo
theology class or even the Daniel in 7
days class um and different individuals
have been trying it uh and it continues
to be refined
but this GPT
uh is basically
taking all the principles of photoology
and showing how you can apply these 36
different principles
36 different rooms
um to any verse in the church. It's
going to help you to take five verses in
the Bible that may look like they have
nothing to do with each other and find
the connecting theme between all five
verses or all 10 verses or two verses or
whatever it is. It's a very powerful
powerful and unique. There is no other
GPT or app out there like this.
Um,
this is not a app that is this is not a
GPT that's going to think for you. It's
a GPT that's going to lead you through
the principles of photo theology. It's
going to build with you instead of
thinking for you. It's designed to lead
you to think more deeply about the
Bible, about the scriptures,
um, and putting thoughts together that
you are putting Yeah. putting thoughts
together that you may have never
in fact
uh the photo
I know
building a photo. And this
is
um within the photo.
Uh this Daniel
GPT
is based on the photo theology.
The third GP is the SDA apologetics GPT.
the SDA Apologetics GPT.
All three of these GPT, the Photo
Theology GPT, the Daniel and Revelation
GPT, and the SDA Apologetics GPT are all
designed
um to take you into a much deeper
understanding of prophecy, of
apologetics, and of the scriptures all
together. So, Jacqueline, um, email me.
Email me, uh, if you can, or I don't
know if you want to
message me. Go on Facebook and message
me and I'll get you
um, reconnected.
Again, for those of you that are in the
Daniel course, which begins tomorrow, it
was supposed to start today, but it will
officially begin tomorrow.
Moto theology.com.
I put the I put the link in the chat
already. Do it again. Myal
the
com. This is where you can sign up for
the revelation
course and we'll begin
sign up
photo theology.
I'm going a live demonstration on this
on my YouTube channel, Power of the Lamb
YouTube. Um, so look out for it. Y'all
are going to be going away. I think
y'all are going away. If you got the the
car deck and you didn't weren't weren't
sure how to use it, um this GPT is going
to is going to assist you and uh you're
going to be blown away
days course, the Daniel and 7 days
course, the photo theology in 7 days
course. Um let me just speak to the
Revelation 7 days course. If you're
trying to join and you think you may not
be able to be present all seven days,
the class is being recorded. So if you
sign up for the course, you will have
access to the classes. It'll be through
website called Mighty Network, power of
the land, Mighty Networks. So you will
join that that uh platform and uh all
the videos, all the like I this is not
your typical revelation class, okay?
You're going to get a bunch of PDFs.
You're going to get a bunch of different
um
lessons from unique angles on the book
of Revelation. And uh you you will not
regret
I'll see you all again soon by God's
grace. All right. Peace. Peace. Peace.